http://www.ashworth.com/privacy-policy

Flat Wire
Positive Drive Chain Edge (PDCE)
Schedule Spiral Service
Privacy PolicyAshworth is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated.From time to time, Ashworth may make changes to its Privacy Policy to reflect changes in its business or to serve you better. Ashworth will use reasonable efforts to publish any such changes in the Privacy Policy.Ashworth's Privacy Policy is based on four basic principles:You will always be advised when Ashworth is collecting information about you or your online preferences and expectations and it will be made clear how that information is to be used.You will be able to choose whether or not you want to provide that information.Any information collected about you will be secure and not shared with any third parties unless you give prior permission for that information to be shared.You will have access to any personal information Ashworth collects and keeps about you and you will be able to securely change or delete that information at any time.Despite any representations concerning privacy, Ashworth reserves the right to disclose without notice to you any information in its possession if required to do so by law or upon a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with the law, to protect or defend our rights or property, or to respond to an emergency situation.Use of cookiesIn order to improve our site, we utilize "cookies" to maintain a record of your visit. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to a web browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. This information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided Ashworth with personal identifiable information. If you do not wish to accept cookies you will find instructions for disabling this function within your browser. ChildrenAshworth's Website is not intended for persons under 13 years of age. Ashworth does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children, and Ashworth does not knowingly market its products or services to children.Links to Other SitesAs a convenience to you, Ashworth's Website may provide links to websites operated by other entities. While Ashworth tries to link only to sites that share Ashworth's high standards and respect for privacy, Ashworth is not responsible for the content, security, or privacy practices employed by such other sites.Changes to this PolicyPlease check this privacy policy periodically to inform yourself of any changes. Although Ashworth reserves the right to modify or supplement this privacy policy, Ashworth will provide notice to you on this Website of any major changes for at least 30 days following such change.CONTACT INFORMATION:Ashworth Bros., Inc.Attention: Web Administrator450 Armour DaleWinchester, VA 22601Phone: 540.662.3494Fax: 540.662.3150Email: ashworth@ashworth.com
